Finding Aid for the Mort Fine Papers PASC.0076
UCLA Library Special Collections
Mort Fine papers
1942-1982
UCLA Library Special Collections
Fine, Morton
PASC.0076
29.0 linear feet (68 boxes, 1 shoe box, and 1 flat box)
There is little biographical information available about Mort Fine. Morton Fine was born in 1916. He teamed with with David Friedkin in the 1940s and together they collaborated on a number of successful radio, television and motion pictue projects over the years. Among their radio projects are Bold Venture, Crime Classics, Broadway is My Beat, and Suspense. By the 1950s the team made the transistion to motion pictures with credits that included Handle with Care and The Pawn Broker, among others. They eventually produced and developed the televsion series I Spy and The Most Deadly Game. Among the many other Mort Fine credits are the radio programs Adventures of Johnny Fletcher, Adventures of Sam Spade, and Escape; the television series Kojak, McCloud, and Streets of San Francisco; and the motion pictures The Greek Tycoon and Caboblanco. He was twice nominated for an Emmy Award for his work on I Spy, and won the Writers Guild Best Written Drama (with Fridekin) for The Pawnbroker (1966). Mort Fine died in 1991.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Mort Fine 1978, 1980, 1984. Additions are the gift of Michael Vernon, 2013.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9912180873606533
Biography/History
There is little biographical information available about Mort Fine. Morton Fine was born in 1916. He teamed with with David Friedkin in the 1940s and together they collaborated on a number successful radio, television and motion pictue projects over the years. Among their radio projects are Bold Venture, Crime Classics, Broadway is My Beat, and Suspense. By the 1950s the team made the transistion to motion pictures with credits that included Handle with Care and The Pawn Broker, among others. They eventually produced and developed the televsion series I Spy and The Most Deadly Game. Among the many other Mort Fine credits are the radio programs Adventures of Johnny Fletcher, Adventures of Sam Spade, and Escape; the television series Kojak, McCloud, and Streets of San Francisco; and the motion pictures The Greek Tycoon and Caboblanco. He was twice nominated for an Emmy Award for his work on I Spy, and won the Writers Guild Best Written Drama (with Fridekin) for The Pawnbroker (1966). Mort Fine died in 1991.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of materials related to the career of writer and producer, Mort Fine. The bulk of collection are scripts, many in bound volumes, for radio, television and motion picture projects. Also included is a very small amount of production information, clippings, ephemera, stories, articles, and other writings by Fine and a small amount of business correspondence and agreements. Among the many radio projects represented in the collection are the series The Adventures of Johnny Fletcher, The Adventures of Sam Spade, Bold Venture, Broadway's My Beat, and Crime Classics. Television projects include Kojak and The Most Deadly Game among others. Motion Picture projects include Cabo Blanco, Greek Tycoon, The Pawnbroker, That Championship Season, and others.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in the following series:
Radio Projects
Television Projects
Motion Pictures Projects
Project Files
Business Records
Unidentified Projects
Short stories, Articles, and Other Writings
Related Material
Collection of Scripts and Production Material for the Television Series I Spy. Available at UCLA Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library.
Mort Fine Papers. Available at UCLA Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library.
Radio writers -- United States -- Archives.; Screenwriters -- United States -- Archives.; Television writers -- United States -- Archives.; Fine, Morton -- Archives; Fine, Morton
- Radio Projects, (1946-1959); Boxes 22-31, 38-45, 48-49, 53, 66, 70
  Organization and Arrangement
  The series is arranged alphabetically by program series titles.
  Scope and Content
  Includes scripts and a small amount of production information, mostly in bound volumes. Programs represented include The Adventures of Johnny Fletcher, The Adventures of Sam Spade, Bold Venture, Broadway's My Beat, Cathy and Elliott Lewis On Stage, Crime Classics, Escape, The Front Page, Hallmark Hall of Fame, The Line-Up, Pursuit, Suspense, and other freelance projects. Some of the bound volumes of Bold Venture contain occasional production information.
  - Adventures of Dick Tracy (The) (audtion script), no date (Box 49)
    General note
    In bound volume labeled Miscellaneous Scripts.
  - Adventures of Johnny Fletcher (The): Episode 1, 1948 May 30 (Box 53)
    In bound volume labeled Adventures of Johnny Fletcher May 30, 1948 to Aug. 22, 1948.
  - Adventures of Johnny Fletcher (The): Episode 2, 1948 June 6 (Box 53)
  - Adventures of Johnny Fletcher (The): Episode 3, 1948 June 13 (Box 53)
  - Adventures of Johnny Fletcher (The): Episode 4, 1948 June 20 (Box 53)
  - Adventures of Johnny Fletcher (The): Episode 5, 1948 June 27 (Box 53)
  - Adventures of Johnny Fletcher (The): Episode 6, 1948 July 4 (Box 53)
  - Adventures of Johnny Fletcher (The): Episode 7, 1948 July 11 (Box 53)
  - Adventures of Johnny Fletcher (The): Episode 8, 1948 July 18 (Box 53)
  - Adventures of Johnny Fletcher (The): Episode 9, 1948 July 25 (Box 53)
  - Adventures of Johnny Fletcher (The): Episode 10, 1948 Aug 1 (Box 53)
  - Adventures of Johnny Fletcher (The): Episode 11, 1948 Aug 8 (Box 53)
  - Adventures of Johnny Fletcher (The): Episode 12, 1948 Aug 15 (Box 53)
  - Adventures of Johnny Fletcher (The): Episode 13, 1948 Aug 22 (Box 53)
  - Adventures of Johnny Fletcher (The): Episode 14, 1948 Aug 29 (Box 53)
    In bound volume labeled Adventures of Johnny Fletcher Aug. 29, 1948 to Nov. 20, 1948.
  - Adventures of Johnny Fletcher (The): Episode 15, 1948 Sept 5 (Box 53)
  - Adventures of Johnny Fletcher (The): Episode 16, 1948 Sept 11 (Box 53)
  - Adventures of Johnny Fletcher (The): Episode 17, 1948 Sept 18 (Box 53)
  - Adventures of Johnny Fletcher (The): Episode 18, 1948 Sept 25 (Box 53)
  - Adventures of Johnny Fletcher (The): Episode 19, 1948 Oct 2 (Box 53)
  - Adventures of Johnny Fletcher (The): Episode 20, 1948 Oct 9 (Box 53)
  - Adventures of Johnny Fletcher (The): Episode 21, 1948 Oct 16 (Box 53)
  - Adventures of Johnny Fletcher (The): Episode 22, 1948 Oct 23 (Box 53)
  - Adventures of Johnny Fletcher (The): Episode 23, 1948 Oct 30 (Box 53)
  - Adventures of Johnny Fletcher (The): Episode 24, 1948 Nov 6 (Box 53)
  - Adventures of Johnny Fletcher (The): Episode 25, 1948 Nov 13 (Box 53)
  - Adventures of Johnny Fletcher (The): Episode 26, 1948 Nov 20 (Box 53)
  - Adventures of Miss Rachel (The): Script, 1949 May 11 (Box 49)
  - Adventures of Sam Spade (The): Blood Money Caper, 1946 Sept 29 (Box 66)
  - Adventures of Sam Spade (The): Buff-Orpington Caper (The), 1947 July 13 (Box 66)
  - Adventures of Sam Spade (The): Caper With Eight Diamonds, 1947 Nov 23 (Box 66)
  - Adventures of Sam Spade (The): Cinderella Caper (The), no date (Box 66)
  - Adventures of Sam Spade (The): Commonwealth Tankard (The), 1947 Aug 10 (Box 66)
  - Adventures of Sam Spade (The): Cosmic Harmony Caper (The), 1947 June 29 (Box 66)
  - Adventures of Sam Spade (The): Dead Duck Caper (The), 1947 Feb 2 (Box 66)
  - Adventures of Sam Spade (The): Dot Marlow Caper (The), 1946 Sept 13 (Box 66)
  - Adventures of Sam Spade (The): Duet in Spades, 1947 May 4 (Box 66)
  - Adventures of Sam Spade (The): Forty-Nine Cent Caper (The), 1947 Sept 7 (Box 66)
  - Adventures of Sam Spade (The): Girl With the Silver Eyes (The), 1947 Feb 9 (Box 66)
  - Adventures of Sam Spade (The): Golden Horseshoe (The), 1946 Dec 29 (Box 66)
  - Adventures of Sam Spade (The): Gutting of Couffignal (The), 1946 Oct 4 (Box 66)
  - Adventures of Sam Spade (The): Jade Dragon Caper (The), 1947 Aug 24 (Box 66)
  - Adventures of Sam Spade (The): Llewelyn Caper (The), 1947 Jan 5 (Box 66)
  - Adventures of Sam Spade (The): Palermo Vendetta Caper (The), 1947 Dec 7 (Box 66)
  - Adventures of Sam Spade (The): Sam and the Unhappy Poet, 1946 July 26 (Box 66)
  - Adventures of Sam Spade (The): Simile Caper (The), 1947 July 6 (Box 66)
  - Adventures of Sam Spade (The): Unwritten Law Caper (The), 1946 Oct 6 (Box 66)
  - Adventures of Sam Spade (The): Wrong Guy Caper (The), 1947 Nov 2 (Box 66)
  - Anacin Hollywood Star Theatre: Reflection of Doom, 1949 Oct 1 (Box 45)
    In bound volume labeled Free Lance Scripts.
  - Bold Venture: Barefoot Goddess With Cheeks, 1958 Oct (Box 25)
    In bound volume labeled Bold Venture Nos. 1B-5B.
  - Bold Venture: Build My Gallows Ankle High, 1959 Jan (Box 26)
    In bound volume labeled Bold Venture Nos. 16B-20B.
  - Bold Venture: Dial M For Mother, 1959 Jan (Box 25)
    In bound volume labeled Bold Venture Nos. 11B-15B.
  - Bold Venture: Episodes 14-26, no dates (Box 22)
    Bound volume labeled Bold Venture Nos. 14-26.
  - Bold Venture: Episodes 27-39, no dates (Box 23)
    Bound volume labeled Bold Venture Nos. 27-39.
  - Bold Venture: Episodes 40-52, no dates (Box 23)
    Bound volume labeled Bold Venture Nos. 40-52.
  - Bold Venture: Episodes 53-65, no dates (Box 24)
    Bound volume labeled Bold Venture Nos. 53-65.
  - Bold Venture: Episodes 66-78, no dates (Box 24)
    Bound volume labeled Bold Venture Nos. 66-78.
  - Bold Venture: Ewell Log (The), 1958 Nov (Box 25)
    In bound volume labeled Bold Venture Nos. 6B-10B.
  - Bold Venture: From Here to Paternity, 1959 Feb (Box 26)
    In bound volume labeled Bold Venture Nos. 21B-25B.
  - Bold Venture: Glittering Skull of Irving Tezcula (The), 1959 Apr (Box 27)
    In bound volume labeled Bold Venture Nos. 31B-35B.
  - Bold Venture: Go Fight Sydney Hall, 1959 Mar (Box 26)
    In bound volume labeled Bold Venture Nos. 26B-30B.
  - Bold Venture: Gun That Wouldn't Quit (The), 1958 Nov (Box 25)
  - Bold Venture: Huckleberry Fine and the Purloined Lox, 1959 Apr (Box 26)
  - Bold Venture: Huckleberry Fine at Trails End, 1959 June (Box 27)
    In bound volume labeled Bold Venture Nos. 36B-39B.
  - Bold Venture: Kazantos, 1959 May (Box 27)
  - Bold Venture: Kick in the Can (The), 1959 Apr (Box 26)
  - Bold Venture: Knock on Any Casket, 1959 Feb (Box 26)
  - Bold Venture: Last Hungry Man (The), 1959 Feb (Box 26)
  - Bold Venture: Look Back, Inge Anger, 1959 May (Box 27)
  - Bold Venture: Look Homeward Morrie, 1959 Feb (Box 26)
  - Bold Venture: Mama George's Horse's Hat, 1958 Oct (Box 25)
  - Bold Venture: Massive Hemmorage of Jamie Kent, 1959 Jan (Box 25)
  - Bold Venture: Matador, 1958 Oct (Box 25)
  - Bold Venture: Naked and the Fat (The), 1958 Nov (Box 25)
  - Bold Venture: Oh Kaplan - My Kaplan, 1959 Jan (Box 26)
  - Bold Venture: Oil For the Lamps of Shannon, 1959 Mar (Box 26)
  - Bold Venture: Olivers Twist, 1959 Mar (Box 26)
  - Bold Venture: One of Our Friedkins Is Missing? Fine, 1959 May (Box 27)
  - Bold Venture: Only the Dead Died Bravely, 1958 Oct (Box 25)
  - Bold Venture: Proud and the Wrinkled (The), 1958 Dec (Box 25)
  - Bold Venture: Red and the Black (The), 1958 Oct (Box 25)
  - Bold Venture: Scripts (1B), 1958 Jan (Box 25)
  - Bold Venture: Shoot Me Slowly, 1958 Dec (Box 25)
  - Bold Venture: Some Came Sleeping, 1959 Mar (Box 26)
  - Bold Venture: Sponger (The), 1958 Dec (Box 25)
  - Bold Venture: Suddenly No Gerson, 1959 Mar (Box 26)
  - Bold Venture: Tom Friedkin Eats Crow, 1959 May (Box 27)
  - Bold Venture: Tom Friedkin Strikes Back, 1959 May (Box 27)
  - Bold Venture: Tom the Fun Loving Freidkin, 1959 Apr (Box 26)
  - Bold Venture: Tom's Brown Schooldays, 1959 May (Box 27)
  - Bold Venture: Tuck High My Shroud, 1959 Jan (Box 26)
  - Bold Venture: Undoing of Huckleberry Fine (The), 1959 May (Box 27)
  - Bold Venture: Whither Thou Goest, Sam?, 1958 Dec (Box 25)
  - Bold Venture: Episodes 1-13, no dates (Box 22)
    Bound volume labeled Bold Venture Nos. 1-13.
  - Broadway's My Beat: Episodes 1-12, 1951 Apr-June (Box 41)
    In bound volume labeled Broadway's My Beat Apr. 7, 1951 to June 30, 1951.
  - Broadway's My Beat: Episodes 1-13, 1949 Nov-1950 Jan (Box 39)
    In bound volume labeled Broadway's My Beat Nov. 5, 1949 to Jan. 31, 1950.
  - Broadway's My Beat: Episodes 1-13, 1951 Sept- Dec (Box 41)
    In bound volume labeled Broadway's My Beat Sept. 15, 1951 to Dec. 8, 1951.
  - Broadway's My Beat: Episodes 13-20, 1951 July-Aug (Box 41)
    In bound volume labeled Broadway's My Beat July 8, 1951 to Aug. 26, 1951.
  - Broadway's My Beat: Episodes 14-26, 1950 Feb- Apr (Box 39)
    In bound volume labeled Broadway's My Beat Feb. 3, 1950 to Apr. 28, 1950.
  - Broadway's My Beat: Episodes 14-26, 1951 Dec- 1952 Mar (Box 42)
    In bound volume labeled Broadway's My Beat Dec. 15, 1951 to Mar. 8, 1952.
  - Broadway's My Beat: Episodes 1-8, 1949 July-Aug (Box 38)
    In bound volume labeled Broadway Is My Beat July 8, 1949 to Aug. 25, 1949.
  - Broadway's My Beat: Episodes 1-9, 1950 Oct-Dec (Box 40)
    In bound volume labeled Broadway's My Beat Oct. 13, 1950 to Dec. 8, 1950.
  - Broadway's My Beat: Episodes 1C-4C, 1952 June-July (Box 43)
    In bound volume labeled Broadway's My Beat June 2, 1952 to July 26, 1952.
  - Broadway's My Beat: Episodes 1C-4C, 1954 July-Aug (Box 45)
    In bound volume labeled Broadway's My Beat July 11, 1954 to Aug. 1, 1954.
  - Broadway's My Beat: Episodes 27-34, 1950 May-June (Box 40)
    In bound volume labeled Broadway's My Beat May 5, 1950 to June 23, 1950.
  - Broadway's My Beat: Episodes 27-37, 1952 Mar-1952 May (Box 42)
    In bound volume labeled Broadway's My Beat Mar. 15, 1952 to May 24, 1952.
  - Broadway's My Beat: Episodes 27-39, 1953 Jan-Apr (Box 43)
    In bound volume labeled Broadway's My Beat Jan. 31, 1953 to Apr. 25, 1953.
  - Broadway's My Beat: Episodes 35-42, 1950 July-Aug (Box 40)
    In bound volume labeled Broadway's My Beat July 3, 1950 to Aug. 21, 1950.
  - Broadway's My Beat: Episodes 40-52, 1953 May-July (Box 44)
    In bound volume labeled Broadway's My Beat May 2, 1953 to July 25, 1953.
  - Broadway's My Beat: Episodes 53-61, 1953 May-Sept (Box 44)
    In bound volume labeled Broadway's My Beat May 27, 1953 to Sept. 26, 1953.
  - Broadway's My Beat: Episodes 62-69, 1953 Oct-Dec (Box 44)
    In bound volume labeled Broadway's My Beat Oct. 3, 1953 to Dec. 4, 1953.
  - Cathy and Elliott Lewis On Stage: Camille, 1954 Jan 27 (Box 49)
  - Cathy and Elliott Lewis On Stage: Cargo, 1953 Jan 11 (Box 49)
  - Cathy and Elliott Lewis On Stage: Corner of Autumn (A), 1952 Nov 23 (Box 49)
  - Cathy and Elliott Lewis On Stage: Dig, the Thief, 1953 Apr 1 (Box 49)
  - Cathy and Elliott Lewis On Stage: Four Meetings, 1953 Feb 19 (Box 49)
  - Cathy and Elliott Lewis On Stage: Saralee, You Are Lovely as the Summer Night, 1954 Sept 5 (Box 48)
  - Cathy and Elliott Lewis On Stage: String Bowtie (The), 1953 Jan 1 (Box 49)
  - Crime Classics: Ali Pasha, A Turkish Delight, 1954 June 23 (Box 31)
    In bound volume labeled Crime Classics Apr. 17, 1954 to June 17, 1954.
  - Crime Classics: Alsop Family: How It Diminished and Grew Again (The), 1953 Aug 24 (Box 29)
    In bound volume labeled Crime Classics June 15, 1953 to Sept. 7, 1953.
  - Crime Classics: Assassination of Abraham Lincoln (The), 1953 Dec 9 (Box 30)
    In bound volume labeled Sept. 30, 1953 to Dec. 23, 1953. Binding broken and volume title missing; appears to be Crime Classics.
  - Crime Classics: Assassination of Leon Trotsky (The), 1954 June 9 (Box 31)
  - Crime Classics: Axe and the Droot Family: How They Fared (The), 1953 Aug 10 (Box 29)
  - Crime Classics: Billy Bonny Bloodletter? also Known as The Kid, 1953 Oct 21 (Box 30)
  - Crime Classics: Blackbeard's Fourteenth Wife: Why She Was No Good For Him, 1953 Nov 11 (Box 30)
  - Crime Classics: Bloody, Bloody Banks of Fall River (The), 1953 Sept 30 (Box 30)
  - Crime Classics: Boorn Brothers and the Hangman: A Study in Nip and Tuck (The), 1954 Jan 27 (Box 30)
    In bound volume labeled Crime Classics Jan. 6, 1954 to Mar. 31, 1954.
  - Crime Classics: Bunny Baumler: His Close Brush With Fame, 1954 May 5 (Box 31)
  - Crime Classics: Cesare Borgia: His Most Difficult Murder, 1954 Apr 21 (Box 31)
  - Crime Classics: Checkered Life and Sudden Death of Col. James Fiske, Jr. (The), 1953 June 29 (Box 29)
  - Crime Classics: Coyle and Richardson? Why They Hung in a Spanking Breeze, 1953 Dec 30 (Box 30)
  - Crime Classics: Crime of Bathsheba Spooner (The), 1953 June 15 (Box 29)
  - Crime Classics: Death of a Baltimore Birdie and Friend (The), 1954 June 16 (Box 31)
  - Crime Classics: Death of a Picture Hanger, 1953 July 20 (Box 29)
  - Crime Classics: Final Day of General Ketchum, and How He Died (The), 1953 July 27 (Box 29)
  - Crime Classics: Francisco Pizarro: His Heart on a Golden Knife, 1954 Mar 24 (Box 30)
  - Crime Classics: General's Daughter, The Czar's Lieutenant and the Linen Closet: A Russian Tragedy (The), 1954 Apr 7 (Box 31)
  - Crime Classics: Good Evening, My Name is Jack the Ripper, 1954 June 30 (Box 31)
  - Crime Classics: Good Ship Jane: Why She Became Flotsam (The), 1954 Feb 24 (Box 30)
  - Crime Classics: Hangman and William Palmer: Who Won (The), 1953 Oct 7 (Box 30)
  - Crime Classics: How Supan Got the Hook Outside Bombay, 1954 Jan 13 (Box 30)
  - Crime Classics: If a Body Need a Body, Just Call Burke and Hare, 1953 Dec 2 (Box 30)
  - Crime Classics: Incredible History of John Shephard (The), 1954 Feb 3 (Box 30)
  - Crime Classics: Incredible Trial of Laura D. Fair (The), 1953 Aug 17 (Box 29)
  - Crime Classics: James Evans, Fireman: How He Extinguished a Human Torch, 1954 Apr 14 (Box 31)
  - Crime Classics: Jean Baptiste Troppmann: Killer of Many, 1954 Feb 17 (Box 30)
  - Crime Classics: John and Judith, Their Crime, and Why They Didn't Get to Enjoy It, 1953 Dec 16 (Box 30)
  - Crime Classics: John Hayes? His Head? and How They Were Parted, 1953 Oct 28 (Box 30)
  - Crime Classics: Killing Story of William Corder and the Farmer's Daughter (The), 1953 Nov 25 (Box 30)
  - Crime Classics: Lethal Habit of the Marquise de Brinvilliers (The), 1954 May 26 (Box 31)
  - Crime Classics: Madeline Smith, Maid or Murderess: Which?, 1954 Jan 20 (Box 30)
  - Crime Classics: Mr. Clark's Skeleton in Mr. Aram's Closet: The Noise It Made, 1954 May 12 (Box 31)
  - Crime Classics: Mr. Jonathan Jewett: How, Most Peculiarly, He Cheated the Hangman, 1954 June 2 (Box 31)
  - Crime Classics: Mr. Thrower's Hammer, 1953 Aug 3 (Box 29)
  - Crime Classics: New Hampshire, the Tiger and Brad Ferguson: What Happened Then, 1954 Mar 10 (Box 30)
  - Crime Classics: Old Six Toes: How He Stopped Construction on the B.B.C. and I, 1954 Mar 17 (Box 30)
  - Crime Classics: Raschi Among the Crocodiles, and the Prank He Played, 1953 Nov 4 (Box 30)
  - Crime Classics: Robby-Boy Balfour: How He Wrecked a Big Prison's Reputation, 1954 Mar 31 (Box 30)
  - Crime Classics: Roger Nems: How He, Though Dead, Won the Game, 1954 Mar 3 (Box 30)
  - Crime Classics: Seven Layered Arsenic Cake of Madame LaParge (The), 1953 Oct 14 (Box 30)
  - Crime Classics: Shockingly Peaceful Passing of Thomas Edwin Bartlett, Greengrocer (The), 1953 June 22 (Box 29)
  - Crime Classics: Shrapnelled Body of Charles Drew, Senior (The), 1953 July 6 (Box 29)
  - Crime Classics: Terrible Deed of Doctor Webster (The), 1953 July 13 (Box 29)
  - Crime Classics: Torment of Henrietta Robinson, and Why She Killed (The), 1953 Sept 7 (Box 29)
  - Crime Classics: Triangle on the Round Table (The), 1953 Nov 18 (Box 30)
  - Crime Classics: Twenty-Three Knives Against Caesar, 1954 Feb 10 (Box 30)
  - Crime Classics: Widow Magee and the Three Gypsies? A Vermont Fandango, 1954 Apr 28 (Box 31)
  - Crime Classics: Younger Brothers: Why Some of Them Grew No Older (The), 1954 Jan 6 (Box 30)
  - Crime Classics: Your Loving Son, Nero, 1953 Aug 31 (Box 29)
  - Escape: Carnival in Vienna, 1954 Sept 11 (Box 48)
  - Escape: Figure a Dame, no date (Box 45)
  - Escape: Mars Is Heaven, no date (Box 45)
  - Escape: Night of the Guns, 1954 July 31 (Box 48)
  - Escape: Outer Limit (The), 1950 Feb 7 (Box 45)
  - Escape: Pass to Berlin, no date (Box 45)
  - Escape: Primitive (The), no date (Box 45)
  - Front Page (The): Episode 1, 1948 May 6 (Box 70)
    In bound volume labeled The Front Page May 6, 1948 to July 22, 1948.
  - Front Page (The): Episode 10, 1948 July 15 (Box 70)
  - Front Page (The): Episode 12, 1948 July 22 (Box 70)
  - Front Page (The): Episode 2, 1948 May 13 (Box 70)
  - Front Page (The): Episode 3, 1948 May 20 (Box 70)
  - Front Page (The): Episode 4, 1948 May 27 (Box 70)
  - Front Page (The): Episode 5, 1948 June 3 (Box 70)
  - Front Page (The): Episode 6, 1948 June 10 (Box 70)
  - Front Page (The): Episode 7, 1948 June 17 (Box 70)
  - Front Page (The): Episode 8, 1948 June 24 (Box 70)
  - Gunsmoke cript, no date (Box 49)
  - Hallmark Hall of Fame: Alphonse Bertillion, 1955 Feb 13 (Box 48)
  - Hallmark Hall of Fame: Daniel, 1954 Nov 28 (Box 48)
  - Hallmark Hall of Fame: Genius of Cremona (The), 1954 Apr 25 (Box 49)
  - Hallmark Hall of Fame: Knute Rockne, 1954 Oct 24 (Box 48)
  - Hallmark Hall of Fame: Mr. Baseball, 1954 May 2 (Box 49)
  - Hallmark Hall of Fame: New Star (The), 1954 Apr 11 (Box 49)
  - Hallmark Hall of Fame: Sarah Siddons, 1954 Dec 12 (Box 48)
  - Hallmark Hall of Fame: Sea of Glory, 1954 May 30 (Box 49)
  - Hallmark Hall of Fame: Shakespeare's Story, 1954 Oct 10 (Box 48)
  - Hallmark Hall of Fame: Sword and Johnny Ring (A), 1954 Mar 28 (Box 49)
  - Hallmark Hall of Fame: William Harvey, 1954 Nov 7 (Box 48)
  - Journey Into Adventure: script, no date (Box 49)
  - Let George Do It: Double-Cross Times Two, 1947 Dec 1 (Box 49)
  - Let George Do It: Murder and Me, 1948 Mar 29 (Box 49)
  - Let George Do It: Murder As a Medium, 1948 May 10 (Box 49)
  - Let George Do It: Sailor Who Loved Sonnets (The), 1947 Dec 29 (Box 49)
  - Let George Do It: Sealed Mystery (The), 1948 Jan 12 (Box 49)
  - Let George Do It: Spade Work For George, 1947 Sept 26 (Box 49)
  - Lineup (The): script, 1950 July - Sept (Box 29)
    In bound volume labeled The Line-Up July 6, 1950 to Sept. 28, 1950.
  - New Adventures of Michael Shayne (The): The Case of the Crooked Wheel, 1948 Mar 24 (Box 49)
  - New Adventures of Michael Shayne (The): The Case of the Purloined Corpse, 1948 Apr 14 (Box 49)
  - Philip Morris Playhouse: Leona's Room, 1949 Feb 25 (Box 49)
  - Police Line-Up (audition script), no date (Box 45)
  - Pursuit: Death Is a Memory, 1949 Dec 9 (Box 45)
  - Pursuit: Script, 1949 Nov 9 (Box 45)
  - Pursuit: The Tear of the Siva, 1949 Nov 25 (Box 45)
  - Romance: Bayou Song, 1952 Sept 25 (Box 49)
  - Romance: Flight to Athens, 1954 Aug 5 (Box 48)
  - Sara's Private Eye - NBC Package Audition (audition script), 1950 Mar 4 (Box 45)
  - Suspense: Around the World, 1953 Apr 6 (Box 28)
    In bound volume labeled Suspense Sept. 28, 1950 to Apr 6, 1953.
  - Suspense: Carnival, 1952 Jan 28 (Box 28)
  - Suspense: Crowd (The), 1950 Sept 21 (Box 28)
  - Suspense: Death of Barbara Allen (The), 1952 Oct 20 (Box 28)
  - Suspense: Destruction, 1954 July 27 (Box 48)
  - Suspense: Fly By Night, 1950 Sept 28 (Box 28)
  - Suspense: Frankie and Johnny, 1952 May 5 (Box 28)
  - Suspense: Joker Wild, 1952 Dec 8 (Box 28)
  - Suspense: Lodger (The), 1948 Feb 14 (Box 49)
  - Suspense: Man Who Cried Wolf (The), 1953 Feb 9 (Box 28)
  - Suspense: Run, Sheep, Run!, 1954 July 13 (Box 48)
  - Suspense: Saint James Infermary Blues, 1953 Feb 23 (Box 28)
  - Suspense: Tom Dooley, 1953 Mar 30 (Box 28)
  - Suspense: Twas the Night Before Christmas, 1951 Dec 24 (Box 28)
  - Undercover Girl (audition script), no date (Box 45)
  - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar: Berlin Matter (The), 1954 Mar 16 (Box 49)